anonews.co 2019-12-17

# Privacy | Anonymous

**Last updated February 22, 2019  **

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at AnonLAB Ltd (“company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

When you visit our website https://www.anonews.co/, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our services.

This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website (such as https://www.anonews.co/), and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy policy as the “ **Sites** “). 

**Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.  **

**TABLE OF CONTENTS  **

1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?

4\. WHO WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH?

5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

6\. DO WE USE GOOGLE MAPS?

7\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?

8\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?

9\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

10\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?

11\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?

12\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

13\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES

14\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

15\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?

16\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  **

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_  ** _We collect personal information that you provide to us such as name, address, contact information, passwords and security data, payment information, and social media login data_.

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when  expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services, when participating in activities on the Sites (such as posting messages in our online forums or entering competitions, contests or giveaways) or otherwise contacting us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Sites, the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect can include the following:

**Name and Contact Data.**  We collect your first and last name, email address, postal address, phone number, and other similar contact data.

**Credentials.**  We collect passwords, password hints, and similar security information used for authentication and account access.

**Payment Data.**  We collect data necessary to process your payment if you make purchases, such as your payment instrument number (such as a credit card number), and the security code associated with your payment instrument. All payment data is stored by our payment processor and you should review its privacy policies and contact the payment processor directly to respond to your questions.

**Social Media Login Data.**  We provide you with the option to register using social media account details, like your Facebook, Twitter or other social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will collect the Information described in the section called “[HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS](https://app.termly.io/dashboard/document-preview/214013#sociallogins)” below.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

**_In Short:_  ** _Some information – such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics – is collected automatically when you visit our Sites._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Sites. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Sites and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Sites, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes. 

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies. 

**Information collected from other sources**

**_In Short:  _** _We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, social media platforms, and other outside sources.  _

We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, social media platforms (such as Facebook), as well as from other third parties. Examples of the information we receive from other sources include: social media profile information (your name, gender, birthday, email, current city, state and country, user identification numbers for your contacts, profile picture URL and any other information that you choose to make public); marketing leads and search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links).  

**2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?  **

**_In Short:  _** _We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent._

We use personal information collected via our Sites for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests (“Business Purposes”), in order to enter into or perform a contract with you (“Contractual”), with your consent (“Consent”), and/or for compliance with our legal obligations (“Legal Reasons”). We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below. 

We use the information we collect or receive: 

  * **To send you marketing and promotional communications.**  We and/or our third party marketing partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time (see the “[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS](https://app.termly.io/dashboard/document-preview/214013#privacyrights)” below).
  * **Deliver targeted advertising to you.**  We may use your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness. 
  * **To protect our Sites.**  We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Sites safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).   

**3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?  **

**_In Short:  _** _We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.  _

We may process or share data based on the following legal basis:

  * **Consent:** We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information in a specific purpose.
  * **Legitimate Interests:** We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.
  * **Performance of a Contract:  **Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.
  * **Legal Obligations:** We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).
  * **Vital Interests:** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:  

  * **Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers.**  We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Sites over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 
  * **Business Transfers.**  We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. 
  * **Third-Party Advertisers.**  We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use information about your visits to our Website(s) and other websites that are contained in web cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
  * **Affiliates.**  We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.     
  * **Business Partners.**  We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.  
  * **Other Users.**  When you share personal information (for example, by posting comments, contributions or other content to the Sites) or otherwise interact with public areas of the Sites, such personal information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Sites in perpetuity. If you interact with other users of our Sites and register through a social network (such as Facebook), your contacts on the social network will see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of your activity, communicate with you within our Sites, and view your profile.

**4\. WHO WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH?  **

**_In Short:  _ ** _We only share information with the following third parties._

We only share and disclose your information with the following third parties. We have categorized each party so that you may be easily understand the purpose of our data collection and processing practices. If we have processed your data based on your consent and you wish to revoke your consent, please contact us.

  * **Advertising, Direct Marketing, and Lead Generation**  
Facebook Audience Network and Google AdSense

  * **Allow Users to Connect to their Third-Party Accounts**  
, Facebook account, Twitter account and Google account

  * **Retargeting Platforms**  
Facebook Custom Audience and Google Ads Remarketing 

  * **Social Media Sharing and Advertising**  
Facebook advertising and Facebook social plugins

  * **Web and Mobile Analytics**  
Google Analytics

**5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**

**_In Short:  _** _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Policy.

**6\. DO WE USE GOOGLE MAPS?  **

**_In Short:  _** _Yes, we use Google Maps for the purpose of providing better service._

This website, mobile application, or Facebook application uses Google Maps APIs. You may find the Google Maps APIs Terms of Service [here](https://developers.google.com/maps/terms). To better understand Google’s Privacy Policy, please refer to this [link](https://policies.google.com/privacy). 

By using our Maps API Implementation, you agree to be bound by Google’s Terms of Service. You agree to allow us to obtain or cache your location. You may revoke your consent at anytime. We use information about location in conjunction with data from other data providers. 

**_In Short:  _** _If you choose to register or log in to our websites using a social media account, we may have access to certain information about you._

Our Sites offer you the ability to register and login using your third party social media account details (like your Facebook or Twitter logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile Information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, e-mail address, friends list, profile picture as well as other information you choose to make public. 

We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy policy or that are otherwise made clear to you on the Sites. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy policy to understand how they collect, use and share your personal information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.   

**8\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?  **

**_In Short:  _** _We are not responsible for the safety of any information that you share with third-party providers who advertise, but are not affiliated with, our websites.  _

The Sites may contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, online services or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Sites. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

**9\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?  **

**_In Short:  _** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will require us keeping your personal information for longer than 2 years.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**10\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?  **

**_In Short:  _** _We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organisational and technical security measures._

We have implemented appropriate technical and organisational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Sites is at your own risk. You should only access the services within a secure environment. 

**11\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

**_In Short:  _** _We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 13 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 13 years of age. By using the Sites, you represent that you are at least 13 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Sites. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

**12\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?  **

**_In Short:  _** _In some regions, such as the European Economic Area, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the [contact details](https://app.termly.io/dashboard/document-preview/214013#contact) provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm> 

**_Cookies and similar technologies:_  ** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Sites visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.  

**13\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES  **

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.

**14\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:  _** _Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information.  _

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Sites, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Sites. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Sites, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.

**15\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?**

**_In Short:  _** _Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**16\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?**

If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by post to:

TheNLBS Ltd  

40 Boroughbridge Road 

BIRMINGHAM, __________ B5 2RH   

United Kingdom
